gbmb.org 2019-04-22

# Privacy Policy

Before using our website, please read our privacy policy.

### Google analytics

Gbmb.org uses Google Analytics to monitor site usage in order to improve the quality of the pages. Google Analytics provides statistical data only for website mangement.  Google Analytics use cookies.  
See: [Google Analytics cookie usage](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage "Google Analytics cookie usage"), [Google privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy "Google privacy policy"). 

### Google Adsense

Gbmb.org uses Google Adsense to display ads.  
Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website or other websites.  
Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads "Ads Settings") and [www.aboutads.info](https://www.aboutads.info/choices "aboutads").  
Adsense serves non-personalized ads to EEA uses.

By using our site, you acknowledge that you have read and understand our privacy policy. Your use of our webiste is subject to these policies.

This website uses cookies to collect information about how you interact with our website. We use this information in order to improve and customize your browsing experience and for analytics and metrics about our visitors. To find out more about the cookies we use, see our Privacy Policy.
